I'm going to let you speak, but let's
not get the attitudes and stuff cuz you
my sister and I respect you. So,
>> I don't have an attitude. I'm being
direct to you.
>> How you domestic violence women or men
are even attacked. What is the first
thing we say? It's like, you know what?
It's not your what? It's not your fault.
So, that's what we do. We hold on to
this narrative that, well, it's not our
fault. And the issues in our community,
they're not our fault. And the white man
needs to give us something. The old
white lady down the street is looking at
me and I don't know why she got braids
in her hair. And we focus on all these
other stupid things that don't matter.
We don't get to the root of the fact
that we're killing each other at a
higher rate than any other race. It is
self-hatred amongst us. I believe that
we can do that. That we my my cousin, my
mom's cousin, excuse me, going coming
from the church parking lot and guess
who stuck her up and robbed her at
gunpoint? A black man.
>> I need you to get to the point.
>> My point is is that No, and I'm not
trying to be funny unless unless like
you said, we're going to keep it
respectful.
>> Yeah, but but you're you're monopolizing
the whole conversation. We're not
>> I'm going to let you speak, but let's
not get the attitudes and stuff cuz
you're my sister and I respect you. So,
>> I don't have an attitude. I'm being
direct to you, but you're literally
speaking this and you're not going to do
that with me either. So, you're stating
your point and you've been stating your
point for quite some time. you have a
proper way for me to respond.
>> Yeah. Would you allow me to respond? So
that's a better response. Go ahead.
>> The response that I have for you is that
everything you're saying does not exist
in a vacuum. I actually agree with you
in that yes, there has been an
incredible denigration of black worth
and black pride in this nation. I think
it's also very important to acknowledge
what has contributed to that and to
state that it is only black people that
have contributed to that is a false
flag. So we have to admit that. So, in
order to have this conversation around
how we got here, you can't say, "Oh,
well, we're caring about the white women
getting braids and that doesn't matter
and this thing." All of that attaches.
All of that is actually a very big part
of the lack of worth of black people.
>> I'll ask you, do you think we're
resilient? What does resilience mean to
you? Do you think we have to be
perpetual victims or do you think that
black people
>> I think that those are two different
conversations. I think there because I
think that the the concept of black
people being victims is really trying to
not provide accountability to where the
root problem for the actual cause is.
And if we keep saying that somebody is a
victim and that that doesn't mean that
the other person should have to have to
actually have accountability, then what
are we really